练习 2-5：辅音到辅音的连读。大声说出每组
Exercise 2-5. Consonant-consonant liaisons. Say the sound of each group of
字母的发音。说字母的音，而不是字母名称。B 是 /b/，不是 bee。共有
letters out loud. The sound of the letter, not the name. B is b, not b. There are
三个大致的发音位置：双唇、牙齿后方，或喉咙。如果一个词
three general locations. The lips, behind the teeth, or in the throat. If a word
以喉咙里发出的声音结尾，而下一个词也以同一
ends with a sound created in the throat, and the next word starts with a sound from
大致位置的声音开头，这些词就会连在一起。
that same general location, these words are going to be linked together. The same
另外两个位置也是一样。跟我读。双唇位置。
with the other two locations. Follow me. At the lips.
牙齿
Behind the
后方。
teeth.
喉咙里。
In the throat.
Grrr